Guide to the Intel Corporation Collection of Inteleads and Other Publications M2254
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Intel Corporation collection of Inteleads and other publications
1976-2001
bulk
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Intel Corporation
M2254
1 Linear Feet: 2 boxes
Contains ten years of Inteleads, Intel Corporation's employee newsletter, as well as other publications.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Note that material must be requested at least 36 hours in advance of intended use.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Anonymous gift, circa 2014.
Related Materials
Stanford Special Collections holds many related collections, including:
Intel Corporation annual and financial reports (M0999) https://searchworks.stanford.edu/view/4084804
Robert Noyce papers (M1490) https://searchworks.stanford.edu/view/6270962
Gordon Moore papers (M1965) https://searchworks.stanford.edu/view/10626780
Andrew S. Grove speeches, 1980-2006 (M1630) https://searchworks.stanford.edu/view/7629938
Scope and Contents
Collection primarily contains ten years of Inteleads, Intel Corporation's employee newsletter. This 1979-1989 run from vol.3 no.6 through vol.13 no.5 is missing only a handful of issues, and includes annual April Fool's editions and other extras. The collection also includes other magazines, promotional booklets, recruitment brochures, users manuals, technical specifications, etc. Intel is a corporation and technology company headquartered in Santa Clara, California that was founded by Gordon Moore and Robert Noyce.
Computer industry -- United States -- History; Microelectronics industry -- California -- Santa Clara County -- History.; Semiconductor industry -- California -- Santa Clara Valley (Santa Clara Valley) -- History -- 20th century -- Sources; Intel Corporation
- Intel University Catalog (Many pages cut out - only remaining ones are instructors' biographies) (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Club Intel, December/January (Box 2, Folder 11)
- MCS-4 Misco Computer Set Users Manual, March 1972 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- 8008 8-Bit Parallel Central Processor Unit, June 1972 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- The Eighty Forty Eight, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Intellec Microcomputer Development System, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- MCS-80/85 Student Notebook, circa 1978 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- A Decade of Leadership: Careers and Technology at Intel, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Fortran-80 Programming Manual, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- SBC 80/05 Single Board Computer Hardware Reference Manual, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- MCS-80/85 System Workshop Summary and Review, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Basic-90 Pocket Reference, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- 8085/8080 Assembly Language Reference Card, March 1979 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- A Revolution in Progress, A History of Intel To Date, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Intelscope Magazine Vol. 8, No. 3, March 1984 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Solutions, November/December 1986 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Introduction to Surface Mount Technology (Application Note), January 1987 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Annual Report, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Intel Credit Union Focus, Spring 1987 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- New Directions in Retirement Planning, 1/1/1988 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Microcomputer Solutions July/August 1989 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Microcomputer Solutions November/December 1989 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Experience Tech for Tomorrow's Games at the Intel Performance Center, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Inteleads Vol. 3, No. 6, June/July 1979 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Inteleads Vol. 3, No. 7, July/August 1979 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Inteleads Vol. 3, No. 8, August/September 1979 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Inteleads Vol. 3, No. 9, September/October 1979 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Inteleads Vol. 3, No. 10, October/November 1979 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Inteleads Vol. 3, No. 11, November/December 1979 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Inteleads, Vol. 4, No. 1, January 1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Inteleads, Vol. 4, No. 2, February 1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Inteleads Vol. 4, No. 3, March 1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Inteleads Vol. 4, No. 4, April 1980 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Inteleads Vol. 4, No. 5, May 1980 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Inteleads, Vol. 4, No. 6, June 1980 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Inteleads Vol. 4, No. 7, July 1980 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Inteleads Vol. 4, No. 8, August 1980 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Inteleads Vol. 4, No. 9, September 1980 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Inteleads Vol. 4, No. 10, October 1980 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Inteleads Vol. 4, No. 12, December 1980 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Inteleads Vol. 5, No. 1, January 1981 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Inteleads Vol. 5, No. 2, February 1981 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Inteleads Vol. 5, No. 3, March 1981 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Inteleads Vol. 5, No. 4, April 1981 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Inteleads Vol. 5, No. 5, May 1981 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Inteleads Vol. 5, No. 6, June 1981 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Inteleads Vol. 5, No. 7, July 1981 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Interleads EXTRA!!: New Benefit: 8 WEEK SABBATICAL, July 17, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Inteleads Vol. 5, No. 8, August 1981 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Inteleads Vol. 5, No. 9, September 1981 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Inteleads Vol. 5, No. 10, October 1981 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Inteleads Vol. 5, No. 11, November 1981 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Inteleads Vol. 5, No. 12, December 1981 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Inteleads Vol. 6, No. 1, January 1982 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Inteleads Vol. 6, No. 2, February 1982 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Inteleads Vol. 6, No. 3, March 1982 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Inteleads Vol. 6, No. 4, April 1982 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Inteleads Vol. 6, No. 5, May 1982 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Inteleads Vol. 6, No. 6, June 1982 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Inteleads Vol. 6, No. 7, July 1982 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Inteleads Vol. 6, No. 8, August 1982 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Inteleads Vol. 6, No. 9, September 1982 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Inteleads Vol. 6, No. 10, October 1982 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Inteleads Vol. 6, No. 11, November 1982 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Inteleads Vol. 6, No. 12, December 1982 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Inteleads Vol. 7, No. 1, January 1983 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Inteleads Vol. 7, No. 2, February 1983 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Inteleads Vol. 7, No. 3, March 1983 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Inteleads Vol. 7, No. 4, April 1983 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Iteleads (April Fools' Day issue), April 1, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Inteleads Vol. 7, No. 5, May 1983 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Inteleads Vol. 7, No. 6, June 1983 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Inteleads Vol. 7, No. 7, July 1983 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Inteleads Vol. 7, No. 8, August 1983 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Inteleads Vol. 7, No. 9, September 1983 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Inteleads Vol. 7, No. 10, October 1983 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Inteleads Vol. 7, No. 11, November 1983 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Inteleads Vol. 7, No. 12, December 1983 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Inteleads Vol. 8, No. 1, January 1984 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Inteleads Vol. 8, No. 2, February 1984 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Inteleads Vol. 8, No. 3, March 1984 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Inteleads Vol. 8, No. 4, April 1984 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Iteleads II (April Fools' Day issue), April 1, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Inteleads Vol. 8, No. 5, May 1984 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Inteleads Vol. 8, No. 6, June 1984 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Inteleads Vol. 8, No. 7, July 1984 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Inteleads Vol. 8, No. 8, August 1984 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Inteleads Vol. 8, No. 9, September 1984 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Inteleads Vol. 8, No. 10, October 1984 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Inteleads Vol. 8, No. 11, November 1984 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Inteleads Vol. 8, No. 12, December 1984 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Inteleads Vol. 9, No. 1, January 1985 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Inteleads Vol. 9, No. 2, February 1985 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Inteleads Vol. 9, No. 3, March 1985 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Inteleads Vol. 9, No. 4, April 1985 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Inteleads Vol. 9, No. 5, May 1985 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Inteleads Vol. 9, No. 6, June 1985 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Inteleads Vol. 9, No. 7, July 1985 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Inteleads Vol. 9, No. 8, August 1985 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Inteleads Vol. 9, No. 9, September 1985 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Inteleads Vol. 9, No. 10, October 1985 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Inteleads Vol. 9, No. 11, November 1985 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Inteleads Vol. 9, No. 12, December 1985 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Inteleads Vol. 10, No. 1, January 1986 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Inteleads Vol. 10, No. 2, February 1986 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Inteleads Vol. 10, No. 3, March 1986 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Inteleads Vol. 10, No. 4, April 1986 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Inteleads Vol. 10, No. 5, May 1986 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Inteleads Vol. 10, No. 6, June 1986 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Inteleads Vol. 10, No. 7, July 1986 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Inteleads Vol. 10, No. 8, August 1986 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Inteleads Vol. 10, No. 9, September 1986 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Inteleads Vol. 10, No. 10, October 1986 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Inteleads Vol. 10, No. 11, November 1986 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Inteleads Vol. 10, No. 12, December 1986 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Inteleads Vol. 11, No. 1, January 1987 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Inteleads Vol. 11, No. 2, February 1987 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Iteleads IV (April Fool's Day issue), April 1, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Inteleads Vol. 11, No. 3, March 1987 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Iteleads (April Fools' Day issue), April 1, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  Scope and Contents
  Includes 7" Eva-tone flexidisc disc recording of Arthur IDIS & the Ethernettes "Cubicle Blues"
- Inteleads Vol. 11, No. 4, April 1987 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Inteleads Vol. 11, No. 5, May 1987 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Inteleads Vol. 11, No. 6, June 1987 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Inteleads Vol. 11, No. 7, July 1987 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Inteleads Vol. 11, No. 8, August 1987 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Inteleads Vol. 11, No. 9, September 1987 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Inteleads Vol. 11, No. 10, October 1987 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Inteleads Vol. 11, No. 11, November 1987 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Inteleads Vol. 11, No. 12, December 1987 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Inteleads Vol. 12, No. 1, January 1988 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Inteleads Vol. 12, No. 2, February 1988 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Inteleads Vol. 12, No. 3, March 1988 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Iteleads (April Fools' Day Issue), April 1, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Inteleads Vol. 12, No. 7, July 1988 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Inteleads Vol. 12, No. 8, August 1988 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Inteleads Vol. 12, No. 9, September 1988 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Inteleads Vol. 12, No. 10, October 1988 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Iteleads (April Fools' Day Issue), April 1, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Inteleads Vol. 13, No. 5, May 1989 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Inteleads Vol. 13, No. 7, July 1989 (Box 2, Folder 9)